tombihn.com 2017-02-23

# Privacy Policy – TOM BIHN

**We don't automatically sign you up for our mailing list. You can choose to sign up here. And even once you're signed up we promise not to send you too much stuff: expect an email newsletter from us every month (or three).**

**We use Google Analytics to help us track the performance of our website. Otherwise, we don't share your information with anyone else. No third parties, no affiliates, no advertisers.**

**You won't get junk in the mail (snail or email) from us. (Tip: use Catalog Choice to save some trees and reduce your snail mail junk load.)**

**Questions or feedback? Email our web team at[feedback@tombihn.com](mailto:feedback@tombihn.com)**

This policy describes how we at TOM BIHN (collectively, "TOM BIHN," "we," or "us") collect, use and share information collected through the mail, TOM BIHN Factory Showroom, and tombihn.com.

## How We Collect And Use Information

### Personally Identifiable Information ("PII")

We may collect personally identifiable information ("PII") such as your name, your contact information, your shipping information, and your billing information (such as credit card account data). We collect PII when you provide it to us through your use of TOM BIHN, for example when you interact with our websites, place an order, or sign up for our mailing list.

We use the PII that we collect to provide TOM BIHN services (such as to process and ship your orders or respond to customer service requests) and to analyze and improve TOM BIHN offerings.

If you register for email or if you provide your email address to us, we will send you emails once every month (or three) about new designs, videos, bag reviews, and other events. We do not share your email address with anyone else.

### Non-Personal Information

We automatically collect certain non-personal information when you use TOM BIHN. For example, we collect information about the devices you use to connect to our services (such as the IP address of your computer or numeric identifier of your mobile device) and about how you use TOM BIHN (such as what time you visit our website).

Our website also uses third-party analytics vendors such as Google Analytics. Please click here for more information about how data is collected and processed in connection with the Google Analytics service: [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). We use analytics data for a variety of purposes, including to improve the user experience of our website.

### Information You Post

All information that you share about yourself, whether PII or not, in a public open forum – such as on our Forums or on a social network – will be considered public information for the purposes of this policy. If you don't want it to be public, please don't post it.

## How We Share Information

We do not disclose your PII to third parties, except as follows:

  * To companies that provide services to us or perform functions on our behalf (such as processing credit card payments) and have agreed to use your information only for the purposes we request;
  * When we believe disclosure is appropriate to enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements, or to protect our rights, our customers, our property, our employees, or others.

## Your Choices

With your PII – like the information you give us to fulfill an order – you have the option to change or correct your information and the choice of not hearing from us again. There are several ways you can control our use of your PII in connection with marketing and promotions.

You are always welcome to unsubscribe from our monthly email list or blog post notifications. To do so, simply click "unsubscribe" at the bottom of one of those emails or click here.

## Correcting or Updating Your Information

If you would like to request changes to the PII that you have previously provided to us, please contact us at [feedback@tombihn.com](mailto:feedback@tombihn.com) or give us a call at 1-800-729-9607.

## Cookies

We may use "cookies," "web beacons," and other similar technologies to collect information in connection with the TOM BIHN website. A "cookie" is a computer file that acts as an identification card for your computer to distinguish your browser from others and enable us to serve you better. For example, we use cookies to save products in your shopping cart while you browse our websites and to track the effectiveness of our marketing and advertising campaigns. Similarly, a "web beacon" is a technology that can recognize specific cookies and convey information about that browser. We do not use these technologies to collect PII.

Most browsers accept cookies automatically. You may be able to set your browser to reject and/or delete cookies. For instructions, check your browser's technical information. However, if you reject or delete cookies then this may disable or interfere with features of the TOM BIHN website or other websites you visit. We recommend that you leave cookies "turned on" so we can offer you a better experience on our site.

## Children

The online TOM BIHN services are not intended for the use of individuals under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect information online from individuals under the age of 13.

## Links to Third Parties and Social Media

Our websites contain links to third-party online properties. Such third parties have their own policies that govern their collection, use, and disclosure of information. We suggest that you read their privacy policies to learn about their practices.

Social media provides tools that many people use and enjoy, and we include links to various social media platforms on our websites. If you interact with these social media tools through our websites, your experience on those social media sites will be governed by the privacy and other policies of those sites. The privacy settings you have chosen on those sites will determine the degree to which your information is made public. We encourage you to choose your privacy settings on those sites accordingly.

## Safeguarding Your Personally Identifiable Information

We have reasonable and appropriate physical, electronic, and administrative measures in place to safeguard the security of your personal information. However, when you communicate with us via email on our websites, these communications may not be encrypted. For that reason, we ask that you do not share sensitive information via these communication channels.

## Updates to the Privacy Policy

If we modify this Privacy Policy, we will post the revised Privacy Policy online. We will notify you if the policy changes in any material way by placing a prominent notice on this web page. You should check regularly to see if this Privacy Policy has changed.
